Subtitles are color-coded by country,
and this setting cannot be changed.
Stand by.
Ready…
Yes! That's it!
Throw her over!
-Don't fall out of bounds!
-Don't fall out!
I tried to throw her over by her leg,
but she didn't even budge.
I guess she's a wrestler for a reason.
Grab her. That's okay.
Grab both of her legs together!
Hang in there!
Her foot is off the edge.
Push her foot off!
Come on, you got this.
Push her now!
Push her off!
Stop.
Game over.
Here is the country surviving
after the second round.
Japan.
Well done! Good job!
Thank you!
I should've held out a bit longer.
If only I'd done a better job.
I kind of beat myself up afterward.
I did it!
NONOKA OZAKI
NATIONAL TEAM WRESTLER
I was ecstatic
that we'd won such an intense match.
I felt a deep sense of pride inside.
I was over the moon
about our win against Korea.
Man, that was just the best.
Now that we're down to
the one final stage,
we absolutely have to make sure
that we win this quest
and earn the right to set the matchups,
as it's an incredible advantage.
It's disappointing
and hard to get over,
but it's actually strengthened my resolve.
Next time we meet, you're dead meat.
I'll crush you.
Just you wait.
Here are the results
of the second round's rematch.
The countries advancing to the third round
are Türkiye and Japan.
Final match.
What do you think their game plan is?
Türkiye
has huge players.
YOSHIO ITOI
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM BASEBALL PLAYER
And from their previous matches,
I got the impression
that they always have a defined strategy.
They had one player who didn't
take part in the game at all.
KANA WATANABE
MMA FIGHTER
There was always a female player
standing on the sidelines, monitoring
the situation and calling out the time.
How many minutes?
One minute and thirty-five seconds.
Thirty-eight seconds!
Watch out, two of them are outside!
Five seconds!
Nefise!
Get up! You have to come!
NEFISE KARATAY
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM TRACK ATHLETE
I noticed that
and shared it with my teammates.
SOICHI HASHIMOTO
NATIONAL TEAM JUDOKA
Let's each mark one of their players…
KANA WATANABE
MMA FIGHTER
…and finish with a one-on-one
between her and Kana.
You know their female wrestler?
I think she's strong.
YASEMIN ADAR YIĞIT
NATIONAL TEAM WRESTLER
We should basically consider her a man.
I guess I'm the one who has to take her.
I was nervous
because our weight classes were different.
She's a world champion
in the highest weight division, the 76 kg,
while I'm in the one below.
I never imagined
I'd face her in a wrestling match.
They're scared of us.
Not to mention tired.
-They're tired.
-They are.
RECEP KARA
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM OIL WRESTLER
Japan and Korea have had many rematches.
Four or five of them, in fact.
We'll win this easily.
YASEMIN ADAR YIĞIT
NATIONAL TEAM WRESTLER
Let's finish this in one go
without going into a rematch.
-Yes, let's do that.
-Yeah.
Make sure we block at least one of them.
The strategy is the same.
Protect us, Allah.
Physical: Asia.
Final round of the territory conquest.
You will fight to conquer…
a single territory.
The game will now begin.
We'll show them
how strong the Japanese are.
We got this. Go Japan!
We, Team Türkiye,
will go all out and claim the victory.
Well said. Short and sweet!
Come on!
PHYSICAL: ASIA
3. SHIPWRECK
Stand by.
Let's go!
Ready…
-Go, go!
-Go!
-Come on! Leg it, leg it!
-That's it!
Take them out. Get them away!
The big guy's going for Okami.
Okami's gone flying.
My sole target
was the leader of Team Japan.
My focus was only on him.
I was in the middle of
fighting other players
when Recep seized me from behind.
That was a painful mistake.
No! Don't let him go!
It was all going to plan.
Each player guards their target,
releasing them at the last minute
to run inside without them.
I thought, "What are these people doing?
What's going on here?"
I was getting nervous
that we were going to lose.
They've pinned down one contestant each.
That's their strategy.
The entire fight is
happening off the territory.
I'm taking her down.
Ali, you just get in here.
She's wrestling
while holding that guy's leg.
That Turkish girl is insanely strong.
I need to dig deep for my team.
Yes! Yes!
Oh, she's…
She's really strong.
Japan is really strong in wrestling.
Wow. Damn.
I was confident that I could beat her,
so I decided to finish it off
right then and there.
Come on, give it everything.
Let's go, girls!
Go!
-Let's go!
Ten seconds.
We need one person!
-Somebody get in here quickly!
-Get in here!
Anyone!
Seven seconds!
Nefise, come on!
Stop! Stay where you are!
Don't move!
Game over.
-Recep got on.
-We won!
We're the winners.
Everyone!
-Look at this right here!
-Bravo!
Bravo!
That was amazing.
Absolutely phenomenal.
At the last second…
SOICHI HASHIMOTO
NATIONAL TEAM JUDOKA
…I got thrown by Anıl, and we lost.
I messed up.
I didn't manage to take Recep down.
Türkiye…
Türkiye ended up winning
despite our best efforts.
Yes, I was mad as hell.
YOSHIO ITOI
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM BASEBALL PLAYER
I haven't been that mad in a long time.
It was especially frustrating
to fall at the last hurdle.
The first quest.
The territory conquest.
The final winner is
Türkiye.
-Good job, Japan.
-Well done, Japan.
-One, two, three, Türkiye!
We've now shown them the power of Türkiye.
NEFISE KARATAY
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM TRACK ATHLETE
We'd do anything for our country.
OGEDAY
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM ROWER
I'm not scared of anyone.
I want to compete against everybody.
Everyone's going to fear us now…
YASEMIN ADAR YIĞIT
NATIONAL TEAM WRESTLER
…because we've proven how strong we are.
Leader.
Thank you.
Türkiye
has won the privilege
to set all the matchups
for the following quest.
-Lucky them.
-All of them?
Yes, all of them.
-No way.
-That's huge.
Prior to setting the matchups,
the keyword for the second quest
will be revealed.
Oh my god!
Physical: Asia.
The keyword for the second quest is…
"shipwreck."
…"shipwreck."
OGEDAY
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM ROWER
We got it. This is ours.
We got it. We can relax now.
We were thrilled
when we heard the keyword.
We assumed it would involve
pulling something up.
You know, something
that requires strength or stamina.
We're also confident
in our explosive power
as well as endurance.
We get to decide the matchups,
so they better be scared of us.
Who should we pick?
I think we should pick
the second team from Japan.
The second team to the right.
They're staring at us.
I'm sure they're targeting us.
That's fine.
That one looks okay too.
So that's Thailand,
and that guy's an actor.
They're picking their opponent.
It could be us.
The Philippines doesn't look bad either.
They're looking at us.
They're thinking that they'll choose us.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, maybe.
We were concerned if
Türkiye would choose us because they won.
So we were a little bit nervous
because they're much bigger than us.
We were fine with
any other team but Türkiye.
JANG EUN-SIL
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM WRESTLER
Lots of teams don't want to face them.
JAMES RUSAMEEKAE
FORMER VOLLEYBALL PLAYER
We also want to avoid them,
as they were strong in the first quest.
Now,
the matchups for the second quest
of Physical: Asia will be announced.
Team Leader of Türkiye, Recep Kara,
please reveal
the first teams in each group.
I guess they'll pit
the strong teams against each other.
I'm so curious to see.
If it's us against Korea,
we'd win, wouldn't we?
Well, we're used to them, at least.
Since Türkiye will have realized
how strong we are,
I expected them to pit us
against a strong team
like Korea or Australia.
I'd be fine with Japan.
Let's settle the score with them.
The matchups will now be revealed.
The Philippines.
Australia is better than Korea.
Well, they've split us up in any case.
The opposing teams
in each group will now be revealed.
Group A.
Please reveal Team Japan's opponent.
Please be good to us.
Of course we'd like a team
with smaller players.
All right, come on.
Australia.
Yeah!
Yeah, they want the strong teams
to destroy each other.
How do you two like that?
We wanted the two strong teams,
Australia and Japan,
to face each other in the opening match.
We're going to win this match!
I think they underestimate us,
so we're going to prove
that Japan is the strongest team here.
We'll show them who's boss.
We're coming for them.
Let's go!
We weren't concerned about
who they were gonna match us up with.
They better watch out
because they're gonna get shipwrecked.
Group B.
Please reveal Mongolia's opponent.
Right, who are we playing against?
Please let us be in Group B.
Group B.
The Philippines.
Well, I guess we've won.
We will make sure
that we win this next level.
Mark my words.
We're going to pull out all the stops…
And win the match.
Let's fight, Philippines.
We'll show them the power
of the Mongolian warriors!
This time, we're not going
easy on the Philippines.
You hear that?
We are going to wipe you out.
Group C.
Please reveal
the Republic of Korea's opponent.
-It's either Indonesia or Thailand.
-Yeah.
It's fine either way.
Group C.
Thailand.
It's us.
-All right. Let's go!
-All right, this is good.
Let's go.
Seeing that we were
going against Thailand,
I thought, "Huh? That's too easy."
It's basically a free pass.
We got this in the bag.
Please root for us.
Listen up, Korea.
PLOY
MUAY THAI COACH
We're going to take you down,
no matter what.
I'm not at all concerned right now.
If Korea has kimchi,
we have som tam.
If Korea has Korean Air,
we have Thai Airways.
If Korea has BLACKPINK's Jisoo,
we have BLACKPINK's Lisa.
We're neck and neck, so let's duke it out.
Group D. Indonesia.
Come on, guys.
Come on, let's fight again.
You guys ready? Let's do this.
-Definitely.
-Oh yeah.
Our flag is red
with the blood of our martyrs,
-and our land is homeland
-through their sacrifices.
Come at us if you dare.
Good luck. You'll need it.
We'll never give up.
We'll keep fighting till the end.
JEREMIAH LAKHWANI
HYBRID ATHLETE
I assure you, it's not gonna be easy.
Yes! Okay, fight me!
Physical: Asia.
This quest will determine
the first countries to be eliminated.
Please prepare for the second quest.
Here again.
Back in the torso heaven.
-"Shipwreck," right?
-"Shipwreck."
What do you reckon?
I feel like this next quest is gonna be
a lot more to our strengths of
-strong, moving shit.
-Yeah.
The previous two seasons,
that's what the next challenge was.
It was loading stuff.
It was loading sand,
and whoever had the most sand.
Hey, morning.
Here they are.
-Morning.
-You ready?
-Let's go.
-Huge day.
-Excited? Excited.
-Yeah, excited.
I have a lot of respect for Japan, but
honestly, it didn't matter
who you put us in there with.
Team Australia was gonna
run through anybody.
What do we think of Australia?
I think they're the strongest team
in Physical: Asia.
Yes, the strongest. And they've got that…
-The power man? The strongman.
-The strongman.
He's definitely going to be strong.
Strongman.
Team Japan, come in.
-You want me to join the team?
-Yes, come in.
Team Australia is all about power.
Power. Yeah.
Yes, that's exactly it.
I think they're dangerous
because they're fearless.
I think we were wrong
about their lack of agility.
Yes, you're right.
-We'll have to operate at 120%.
-That's right.
-Still, we're well-balanced.
-Yes, we're the most balanced.
Don't underestimate them, by the way.
Everyone's world-class.
-Our opponents today? Japan.
-Yeah.
I respect them,
but they're not friends
until after this whole thing.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, absolutely.
All right, guys,
let's absolutely decimate this one.
I'm more confident than ever.
This is how strong we are.
Come and get us.
With our agility, speed, and smarts,
along with our strength,
we will prevail over Australia's power.
-Let's go, guys!
-Japan, let's go!
-What?
-Wow.
-What the hell.
Holy moly.
This is unreal!
-Wow, it's a shipwreck.
-Amazing. We're here.
So this is it.
It made me wonder what we were doing.
Oh my goodness.
Yes! Water?
Water, sand.
What's with the water?
Can you swim in it?
It's a bit shallow.
But you can with a bit of effort.
-That looks like a prison.
-We can chuck them in here.
-I think you're right.
-There is a prison.
-It looks like a prison.
-I think you're right.
Maybe if you tag them,
they have to go to jail.
Playing on giant kids' stuff,
so I can't wait to do it.
Physical: Asia.
The second quest determining
the first country to be eliminated
will now begin.
The second quest is…
the shipwreck transportation match.
-Yes.
I felt like I was in
Pirates of the Caribbean.
It was like an actual shipwreck.
You know, it was unreal.
I'd never seen such an epic set.
I was impressed.
YOSHIO ITOI
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM BASEBALL PLAYER
The shipwreck transportation match.
In the wreck are six tons of goods,
and your goal is to move as much of it
as possible to your respective camps.
Six tons.
Six tons?
Shit, this is crazy.
The goods to be transported
consist of crates and bags.
The crates must be
transported by zip line,
while the bags must be
transported by cart.
Those assigned to the zip line
may not switch roles at any point.
Whoever does crates can only do crates
for the rest of the game.
Assigning roles is going to be important.
The duration is 20 minutes.
Please start your strategy meeting.
We'll start with all five of us
bringing the goods over.
The men will first bring 4 50 kg crates.
-And put them around here.
-Yes, over there.
We'll start off with four crates.
We figured the way we transported
the 50 kg crates to the other side
would be the key to winning.
We assigned this task to Hashimoto,
since he has both agility and strength.
SOICHI HASHIMOTO
NATIONAL TEAM JUDOKA
-I'm excited.
-Let's go, buddy.
Twenty minutes in the air. I got it.
There is no one
who is more comfortable in the air.
I figured I should slip into the role.
For tasks that involve
a lot of physical exertion,
it's better to go at a steady pace.
And remember, guys, we got to be flexible.
Let's say, shit starts happening.
Everyone's doing something. No dead time.
Yup. Communication.
Now,
the second quest of Physical: Asia.
The shipwreck transportation match.
-Twenty minutes. We have to work smart.
-Let's go!
Once the whistle blows,
-the game will begin.
-Yeah, I'm ready, bro.
Stand by.
We're not leaving the competition yet.
I do what needs to be done
for my team to win.
That's what I'm here for.
Ready…
Take your time.
-Let's go, bro. Enjoy.
-Good luck.
Yes, Eloni.
It's sturdy.
There were a lot of obstacles.
Oh, so it's like this.
-Can you manage it alone?
-We'll go together.
As the two of us were lugging the crate…
we saw the rugby guy with one to himself.
Let's go, team. Come on.
Things weren't looking too good.
Leave it there.
All right. Bring her up, Eddie.
Off you go, Eloni.
You had to watch the steps
really carefully
because it was so like, vertical.
It feels much heavier.
-Come on.
-It's crushing my hand.
Leave it there. Go, go.
Go, go, I got it. Go.
-You good?
-Yup.
Careful.
Yeah, perfect. Thank you.
I knew he had an advantage in the air,
so I was frantically trying to keep up.
I knew I had to speed things up.
I need a crate right now!
Two men on Japan's crates.
I think that just gives us
a boost of confidence.
Beautiful.
Slide it down.
Good job. Leave it there.
Yup. Go.
Leave the bags at the bottom!
Okay, while everyone's here,
throw me the bags.
Okay. Bags.
Eddie was gonna be the big man.
He was gonna be that middleweight,
and me and Eloni
were just gonna run back and forth.
As hard as we can, we'll win.
Beat any team at any challenge.
Okay.
5TH CRATE, 3RD CRATE
I decided to compete on speed,
making more trips than Team Australia.
Let's go.
There was no escaping the fact
that there was
a huge difference in stamina.
But we were able to transport
the sandbags at a decent pace.
KATSUMI NAKAMURA
NATIONAL TEAM SWIMMER
Let's move them now.
And they were accumulating
faster than we expected.
Let's go!
It had been a tactical decision
to make more frequent trips.
Here goes.
-Should we give this a go then?
-Let's do it.
7 BAGS
Two, three.
I was stunned
when we first pushed the cart.
It was really heavy.
-Go.
-Set your foot down.
It was a coordinated movement
where one person took a step forward
while the other pushed the cart.
Two, three.
It required a lot more skill
than you might think.
Ten minutes left.
Revealing the interim weight score.
We're ahead of them!
I was stunned.
I thought we might have a chance.
Yes!
I have every confidence
that we can win this.
Keep it up!
Wow, we didn't expect it.
Did they swap the scores around?
What was going on?
But also, we're still in the game.
We've just got to move on.
As they've made me team captain,
I feel like it is my responsibility.
Come here.
So if we saw crates needing help,
we were moving on crates.
Let's go!
Almost halfway. Let's go.
If we saw the bags were piling up,
we got the bags down the chute.
Ten, twenty, kids.
We were also going to
have to switch on a dime
depending on who needed what.
Okay, let's push.
14 BAGS
Heavy?
The first time me and Eloni
pushed the cart,
I thought to myself, "Oh, shit."
On that thing, I think we loaded
about 400-odd kilos in it.
We both really struggled.
No movement at all.
One, two, three, go. Almost there.
Let's go!
It was tricky.
We almost died two or three times.
Good shit, boys!
-Good shit, boys!
-Let's go!
Yeah, it was heavy.
We threw our first load in the minecart.
1ST CART, 4TH CART
Five bags at a time is good.
We went up at lightning speed,
making a good number of trips.
If we keep moving at speed,
I'm sure we'll be able to
accumulate enough to beat Australia.
I'm going to give it everything I've got
to win this.
You good?
More sandbags, please!
Go for the sandbags if possible!
I'm not giving up.
Is this it?
There are no crates!
They're all gone!
It hadn't occurred to us
that we could run out of crates.
5 MINUTES AGO
Take that one, Dom. This is the last one.
So I'm coming across,
and my team is telling me
there are no more crates.
But then I look to the right and notice
Japan hasn't finished
loading their crates.
Grab one of their boxes!
Then they can't catch up!
Dom was the one that was like,
our eyes in the sky.
Good shit, girls.
That's the way to do it.
They can't catch us if the boxes are out.
-Leave it.
-You smashed it.
Good shit, Rob. I got it.
-Come on, let's go faster.
-That's the last one.
Let's go!
Get it.
And then we ended up taking
some of Japan's crates as well.
I saw toward the end
that Australia was stealing our crates.
We were all furious.
I realized if we could take
some of Japan's crates,
there was no way
that they could catch up to us.
So there was Hashimoto,
left with nothing to do.
However, instead of giving up,
I focused all my attention
on what I could do.
-Hey, let's have fun!
-All right!
Let's enjoy the experience!
Four minutes to go!
I know this is brutal, but we're close!
Give it one final push! Step it up, guys!
I knew we could take this.
Hang in there, not long now!
My muscles were screaming.
Straight for the win.
Yes, Eloni, you f****** animal!
Let's go!
Bring them up. Yes, Rob!
Three minutes!
Three minutes! Two fifty, come on!
Keep pushing, guys, keep pushing!
Just one more!
Everyone, come here!
Hey, come down!
Let's go!
One forty-five. Everyone, push the cart!
Let's go, team. Bring it! Bring it!
Chain game!
Push it up!
Let's go! Hurry!
-One thirty!
-We've got time.
Push the cart!
We're okay on sandbags!
We don't need any more sandbags!
Hey, let's all push it up together!
Go!
Everyone, get down here!
All right, I'm going up.
All right, push it up!
One twenty!
Push!
Go, go. Start, start.
Go! Push!
Let's go!
It felt like we'd pushed
the pedal down in a car.
Like we went full throttle.
Let's go!
This is us! Let's go!
Last minute!
Everyone, push!
Push his lower back!
We didn't let up till the end.
We all came together for the final push.
This is us!
Let's go! Last minute!
-Unload!
Let's unload.
Come on, everyone! Let's do this together!
That's it, easy money!
Thirty-five, thirty seconds to go!
Keep going!
You can get it. You can get one bag.
We don't quit!
Come on! Keep going till the end!
Let's all do this together!
-Okay, now go!
-Go!
Go, push!
Seven! Six!
All right, let's go!
It's come off the rails!
Stop.
Game over.
Nice fight!
Yes!
Bags, crates, everything.
You guys were amazing.
-Let's go.
-Amazing.
Great job, everyone!
Thank you.
Nice.
Good job.
The second quest of Physical: Asia.
The shipwreck transportation match.
Here are the results
of Japan versus Australia.
Look at those crates stacked up.
We can do this.
Japan.
1,820 kg.
Really good job. That's a lot.
-Two tons.
-Well done.
You moved two tons.
Australia.
Two, give us two.
2,100 kg.
The winning team is
Team Australia.
Yes!
JAPAN
18 CRATES, 46 BAGS
AUSTRALIA
22 CRATES, 50 BAGS
We did our absolute best.
It's just that Australia
happened to be stronger.
I didn't at all expect us to lose.
I'm so mad.
It's devastating.
I sincerely apologize to my team.
Genuinely the best feeling ever.
Our endorphins were just out of control.
So we were on a huge high.
We were so excited.
The key factor for winning quest two
was teamwork.
Without a doubt, it was teamwork.
Yeah, I'm very proud.
I feel like the team
is becoming a family even more.
Time to throw it. Get that out.
Oh, this is legitimately…
-Oh my gosh.
-Wow.
It's a shipwreck.
There's a shipwreck.
The second quest of Physical: Asia
is the shipwreck transportation match.
…transportation match.
-Yeah.
-All right, all right.
In the wreck are six tons of goods,
and your goal is to move as much of it
as possible to your respective camps.
The crates must be
transported by zip line,
while the bags must be
transported by cart.
The duration is 20 minutes.
Because the thing is,
it might be more efficient.
We have to focus on those bags because
three is already more than one crate.
-Yeah.
-But 50 kg is not that heavy.
-Is it manageable?
-Yeah.
I can do the crates.
I assigned the roles to each member.
We assigned Ray to carry the boxes.
And also, Robyn was on the rope.
This is what I think.
Let's forget about the sandbags.
We should transport the crates first.
-And Ochir will go up, right?
-Yeah.
LKHAGVA-OCHIR
CIRCUS ARTIST
I'd already assumed the role was mine
as soon as I saw it.
Team Mongolia,
they're gonna go home after this.
-Yeah, 100%.
-Yeah, of course, 100%.
Send them home, Manny.
We'll send them home.
-Definitely. Let's get in here.
-Yeah!
-Let's go!
-Let's fight!
-Philippines!
Mongolia is a strong team.
But we can beat them with our strategy.
My focus is on winning.
-Warriors, mount up!
-Mount up!
ORKHONBAYAR
BÖKH WRESTLER
Whatever strategy Team Philippines uses
is of no concern to us.
We're just going to focus
on our own strategy.
Stand by.
Get ready to roll, guys.
Ready…
Let's go. Come on!
Mongolians! Charge!
Go, go. Let's go!
Pick up, guys.
It's 20 kg each.
So we focused exclusively on the bags.
And also, there's…
We assigned Ray to carry the boxes.
I'm good. Go, go. Ray, go.
The reason is because
I'm the lightest out of everyone
and the quickest.
So we agreed that my speed
would be able to sail me across the ship.
We're doing our tasks already,
as I notice the other team
doing a two-man job.
-Here, take this.
-Okay. Khandsuren, let's begin.
The crates weren't actually that heavy,
but we had to carry them
across the water and up the slope.
It was tough for one person to do
many times, so we did it as a relay.
One crate, two guys carrying it,
and it's very efficient.
We should have adjusted our strategy.
RAY
STRONGMAN
Crates!
Let's share one. Come on, let's go.
The crates are very big and bulky.
It's not just an easy lift.
You have to have balance,
and it's really tricky.
Come on!
-Let's go, guys!
-Come on!
I got it.
Good. Go, go. Ray, go.
The first thing that crossed my mind
when I pulled a crate was,
I really underestimated the weight.
And then, I'm running out of breath.
Our strategy was to focus on the crates
for the first ten minutes.
We brought the crates over first
so that Ochir could
keep transporting them.
Ropes are used widely in circuses,
in trapezes and whatnot,
so this was right up my alley.
Breathe, Ray. You got this.
Keep breathing, you got it.
Ray!
Focus.
I saw Ray having a difficult time.
That's why I started telling him…
Ray! Come down here and move the bags.
I gave him a different role
so he could help the team.
You got this, Ray.
Come on, guys!
I kept on telling myself,
"You really have to keep pushing."
"Do not give up. Help your team."
I hated the thought of losing.
I wanted to win,
so I continued to move the bags.
Down this way!
Lift it up here.
Put it over.
You going to be okay?
-Yeah, I can take more.
-One more?
Yeah, come on.
-No, I'll take this one in my hand.
-Okay, be careful.
Upholding the honor of your country
is important here.
We're here to win the championship.
I cried out,
driven by my determination to win.
Manny. I can see the motivation
and his dedication for the team.
I think for me,
that was my motivation also,
so that I wouldn't
stop the transportation.
-One, two.
-Bring over some bags.
-Yeah, they're coming.
We all bring crates and pile them up here.
Once Ochir starts slowing down,
we leave the crates,
bring as many bags as we can,
and chuck them down there.
Look, spin as you throw it
over your shoulder.
That's it.
Carry them on your shoulder.
Here, put them on your shoulder.
There you go.
Some of the bags being tied together
actually worked to my advantage.
I thought, "This is great.
The more the better."
It was perfect for carrying
several of them in one go.
All right, get down there!
Get down there and load them up!
Come on, guys.
7 BAGS
Come on!
Get low, guys! Push low!
Yes! Push low, guys.
Next step, come on.
Next step.
Let's unload.
This one's f****** 80 kilos.
This one's 80 kilos.
-One, two, three!
-Two, three.
Ten minutes.
Ten minutes left.
Ten minutes. Come on!
Revealing the interim weight score.
Damn.
We're the same!
We're 400 each!
Subtitle translation by: Jee Butcher